Finding Aid for School of Public Health (University of Michigan) Records 1909-2015 (bulk 1941-2006).
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Dean June E. Osborn, 1984-1989
  - Annual Files, 1988
    - University
      - Vice President for Research (L. Wilson), 1988 (Box 60)
      - Vice Provost for Medical Affairs, 1988 (Box 60)
      - Vice Provost for Minority Affairs, 1988 (Box 60)
  - Annual Files, 1989
    - Administration
      - AIDS
        - General, 1989 (Box 61)
        - Correspondence
          - A-I, 1989 (Box 61)
          - J-Q, 1989 (Box 61)
          - R-Z, 1989 (Box 61)
        - Presentations, 1989 (Box 61)
      - Appointments and Promotions, 1989; 4 folders (Box 63)
        [Restricted until December 31, 2019 ]
      - Development Office, 1989 (Box 61)
      - Koop, C. Everett (Surgeon General), 1989 (Box 61)
      - Student Affairs, Office of, 1989 (Box 61)
      - Students, 1989; 1 folders (Box 63)
        [Restricted until December 31, 2064 ]
    - Committees
      - Curriculum Committee, 1989 (Box 61)
      - Executive Committee
        - General, 1989 (Box 61)
        - Minutes, 1989 (Box 61)
        - Retreat Material, 1989 (Box 61)
      - Faculty Meetings, 1989 (Box 61)
      - Human Subjects Review Committee, 1989 (Box 61)
    - Departments
      - Biostatistics (G. Kalton), 1989 (Box 61)
      - Community Health Programs, 1989 (Box 61)
      - Environmental and Industrial Health, 1989
        - Low Level Radioactive Waste, 1989 (Box 61)
        - NIOSH Site Visit and Training Grant Application, 1989; 2 folders (Box 61)
      - Epidemiology (D. Schottenfeld), 1988-1989; 1 folders (Box 63)
      - Health Behavior and Health Education (N. Clark), 1989 (Box 61)
      - Health Services Management and Policy (J. Griffith), 1989 (Box 61)
      - Population Planning and Industrial Health (G. Simmons), 1989 (Box 61)
      - Public Health Policy and Administration (G. Pickett), 1989 (Box 61)
    - State
      - Ann Arbor, 1989 (Box 61)
      - Battle Creek
        - W.K. Kellogg Foundation, 1989 (Box 61)
      - Detroit
        - General (Includes Greater Detroit Area Health Council), 1989 (Box 61)
        - Wayne County Ad Hoc Group on AIDS, 1989 (Box 61)
      - Lansing
        - General, 1989 (Box 61)
        - Governor's task Force on Access to Health Care, 1989 (Box 61)
        - Michigan Department of Public Health, 1989 (Box 61)
        - Public Health Advisory Council, 1989 (Box 61)
    - University
      - Campus Miscellaneous, 1989 (Box 61)
      - Academic Planning and Analysis, 1989 (Box 61)
      - Horace H. Rackham School of Graduate Studies (J. D'Arms), 1989 (Box 61)
      - Institute of Gerontology, 1989 (Box 61)
      - Medical School
        - General, 1989 (Box 61)
        - Department of Pediatrics and Communicable Diseases, 1989 (Box 61)
      - Office of the President, 1989 (Box 61)
      - Presidential Initiatives Fund (Contact Pattern, Risk Factors, and Dynamic Analyses of HIV Transmission), 1989 (Box 61)
      - Vice President for Academic Affairs
        - General, 1989 (Box 61)
        - Charles Vest, 1989 (Box 61)
      - Vice President for Research (L. Wilson), 1989
        - Biotechnology Retreat, 1989 (Box 61)
      - Vice Provost for Minority Affairs, 1989 (Box 61)
  - Annual Files, 1990
    - Administration
      - American Public Health Association Annual Meetings, 1990 (Box 64)
      - Community and Government Relations, 1990 (Box 64)
      - Correspondence
        - General
          - A-I, 1990 (Box 64)
          - J-Q, 1990 (Box 64)
          - R-Z, 1990 (Box 64)
        - Foreign, 1990 (Box 64)
      - Development Office, 1990
        - General, 1990 (Box 64)
        - Public Health Alumni Society, 1990 (Box 64)
      - General, 1990 (Box 64)
      - Memos to Dept. Chairmen, 1990 (Box 64)
      - New Faculty Appointments
        - General, 1990 (Box 95)
          [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2020 ]
        - Philips, James, 1990 (Box 95)
      - Office for the Study of Aging (OSA), 1990 (Box 64)
      - Recruitment for School, 1990 (Box 95)
      - Spires of Excellence Responses, 1990 (Box 64)
      - Students, 1990 (Box 64)
      - Student Associations, 1990 (Box 64)
    - Committees
      - Advisory Committee on Academic Rank,1990, 4 folders (Box 95)
      - Executive Committee
        - General, 1990 (Box 64)
        - Minutes, 1990 (Box 64)
      - Faculty Meetings, 1990 (Box 64)
    - Departments
      - Biostatistics
        - General, 1990 (Box 64)
        - External Review, 1990 (Box 64)
        - Kalton, Graham, 1990 (Box 64)
        - Cornell, Dick, 1990 (Box 64)
        - On Job Off Campus (OJOC) Mock Study Section, 1990 (Box 64)
      - Community Health Programs
        - General, 1990 (Box 64)
        - Burt, Brian, 1990 (Box 64)
        - Grinker, Joel, 1990 (Box 64)
      - Environmental and Industrial Health
        - General, 1990 (Box 64)
        - Gray, Bob, 1990 (Box 64)
        - Selby Discussional, 1990 (Box 64)
      - Epidemiology
        - General, 1990 (Box 64)
        - Schottenfeld, David, 1990 (Box 64)
      - Health Behavior and Health Education
        - General, 1990 (Box 64)
        - Clark, Noreen, 1990 (Box 65)
      - Health Services Management and Policy
        - Griffith, John, 1990 (Box 65)
      - Population Planning and International Health
        - General, 1990 (Box 65)
        - Simmons, George, 1990 (Box 65)
        - Population Environment Dynamics, 1990 (Box 65)
      - Public Health Policy and Administration
        - General, 1990 (Box 65)
        - External Review, 1990 (Box 65)
        - Pickett, George, 1990 (Box 65)
    - National
      - Washington D.C.
        - General, 1990 (Box 65)
        - Public Health Service, 1990 (Box 65)
    - State
      - Michigan Dept. of Public Health, 1990 (Box 65)
    - University
      - Division of Health Sciences, 1990 (Box 65)
      - Dept. of Research Development and Administration, 1990 (Box 65)
      - General, 1990 (Box 65)
      - Horace H. Rackham Graduate School
        - General, 1990 (Box 65)
        - Office of the Dean of Graduate Studies, (John H. D'Arms), 1990 (Box 65)
      - Hospitals, 1990 (Box 65)
      - Institute of Gerontology, 1990 (Box 65)
      - Institute for Social Research, 1990 (Box 65)
      - Michigan SEA Grant Policy Committee, 1990 (Box 65)
      - News Service, 1990 (Box 65)
      - Office of the Provost, (Charles M. Vest), 1990 (Box 65)
      - Regents, 1990 (Box 65)
      - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs and University Senate, 1990 (Box 65)
      - University of Michigan Corporate Update, 1990 (Box 65)
  - Annual Files, 1991
    - Administration
      - Correspondence
        - General
          - A-I, 1991 (Box 65)
          - J-Q, 1991 (Box 65)
          - R-Z, 1991 (Box 65)
        - Foreign, 1991 (Box 65)
      - Development Office
        - General, 1991 (Box 65)
        - Public Health Alumni Society, 1991 (Box 65)
      - Memos
        - To Dept. Chairmen, 1991 (Box 65)
        - To Faculty Members, 1991 (Box 65)
      - Promotions
        - General, 1991 (Box 95)
          [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2021 ]
        - Memos Regarding, 1991 (Box 95)
      - Students, 1991 (Box 95)
        [SR RESTRICTED until July 1 2066 ]
      - Student Associations, 1991 (Box 65)
        [ER RESTRICTED until July 1, 2066 ]
    - Committees
      - Executive Committee
        - General, 1991 (Box 65)
        - Minutes, 1991 (Box 65)
      - Faculty Meetings, 1991 (Box 65)
    - Departments
      - Biostatistics
        - General, 1991 (Box 65)
        - Chair Search Committee, 1991 (Box 95)
        - Cornell, Dick, 1991 (Box 65)
      - Community Health Programs
        - General, 1991 (Box 65)
        - Burt, Brian, 1991 (Box 65)
      - Environmental and Industrial Health
        - General, 1991 (Box 65)
        - Gray, Bob, 1991 (Box 65)
        - Mancy, Hosney, 1991 (Box 66)
      - Epidemiology
        - General, 1991 (Box 66)
        - Schottenfeld, David, 1991 (Box 66)
        - Maassab, John, 1991 (Box 66)
        - Payne Fellowship, 1991 (Box 66)
      - Health Behavior and Health Education
        - General, 1991 (Box 66)
        - Clark, Noreen, 1991 (Box 66)
      - Health Services Management and Policy
        - General, 1991 (Box 66)
        - Griffith, John, 1991 (Box 66)
        - Wheeler, John, 1991 (Box 66)
      - Population Planning and International Health
        - General, 1991 (Box 66)
        - Takeshita, Yuzuru, 1991 (Box 66)
      - Public Health Policy and Administration
        - General, 1991 (Box 66)
        - Romani, John, 1991 (Box 66)
    - National
      - Washington D.C.
        - General, 1991 (Box 66)
        - Public Health Service, 1991 (Box 66)
    - State
      - Ann Arbor, 1991 (Box 66)
      - Lansing, 1991 (Box 66)
      - Michigan Cities, 1991 (Box 66)
      - Michigan Department of Public Health, 1991 (Box 66)
    - University
      - General, 1991 (Box 66)
      - Institute of Gerontology, 1991 (Box 66)
      - Michigan SEA Grant Policy Committee, 1991 (Box 66)
      - Office of the Dean of Graduate Studies, (John H. D'Arms), 1991 (Box 66)
      - Office of the Provost, (Gilbert R. Whitaker)
        - General, 1991 (Box 66)
        - Hollingsworth, Peggie, 1991 (Box 95)
      - Office of the President, 1991 (Box 66)
      - Office of University Relations, Public Service Database, 1991 (Box 66)
      - Office of the Vice President for Academic Affairs, (Bob S. Holbrook), 1991 (Box 66)
      - Office of the Vice President for Minority Affairs, (Charles D. Moody), 1991 (Box 66)
      - Office of the Vice President for Research, (William C. Kelly), 1991 (Box 66)
      - Other Schools and Colleges., 1991 (Box 66)
      - Regents, 1991 (Box 66)
  - Annual Files, 1992
    - Administration
      - Associate Professor Merit Review Letters, 1992 (Box 95)
        [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2022 ]
      - Correspondence
        - General
          - A-C, 1992 (Box 66)
          - D-J, 1992 (Box 66)
          - K-Q, 1992 (Box 66)
          - R-Z, 1992 (Box 66)
        - Foreign, 1992 (Box 66)
      - Development Office, 1992 (Box 66)
      - General, 1992 (Box 66)
      - Memos to Dept. Chairmen, 1992 (Box 66)
      - Memos to Faculty Members, 1992 (Box 66)
      - New Faculty Appointments, 1992 (Box 95)
      - Office for the Study of Aging (OSA), 1992 (Box 66)
      - Secretary of Faculty, 1992 (Box 66)
      - Self-Study Report, 1992 (Box 66)
      - Students, 1992 (Box 95)
    - Committees (Box 67)
      - Executive Committee
        - General, 1992 (Box 67)
        - Minutes, 1992 (Box 67)
      - Faculty Meetings, 1992 (Box 67)
      - General, 1992 (Box 67)
    - Departments
      - Biostatistics
        - General, 1992 (Box 67)
        - Cornell, Dick, 1992 (Box 67)
      - Community Health Programs
        - General, 1992 (Box 67)
        - Burt, Brian, 1992 (Box 67)
        - Garn, Stanley, Retirement Symposium, 1992 (Box 67)
      - Environmental and Industrial Health
        - General, 1992 (Box 67)
        - Industrial Hygiene Discussional, 1992 (Box 67)
        - Mancy, Hosney, 1992 (Box 67)
      - Epidemiology
        - General, 1992 (Box 67)
        - Maassab, John, 1992 (Box 67)
      - Health Services Management and Policy
        - General, 1992 (Box 67)
        - Clark, Noreen, 1992 (Box 67)
        - Wheeler, John, 19912Population Planning and International Health (Box 67)
        - General, 1992 (Box 67)
        - Takeshita, Yuzuru, 1992 (Box 67)
      - Public Health Policy and Administration
        - General, 1992 (Box 67)
        - Warner, Ken, 1992 (Box 67)
    - National
      - Washington D.C.
        - Public Health Service, 1992 (Box 67)
    - State
      - Lansing, 1992 (Box 67)
      - Michigan Dept. of Public Health, 1992 (Box 67)
      - Michigan Women's Foundation, 1992 (Box 67)
    - University
      - General, 1992 (Box 67)
      - Institute for Social Research, 1992 (Box 67)
      - Medical School, 1992 (Box 67)
      - Michigan Journal of Fellows, 1992 (Box 67)
      - Office of the Dean of Graduate Studies, (John H. D'Arms), 1992 (Box 67)
      - Office of the President, (James J. Duderstadt)
        - General, 1992 (Box 67)
        - Academic Affairs, 1992 (Box 67)
      - Office of the Provost, (Gilbert R. Whitaker)
        - General, 1992 (Box 67)
        - Meeting of, October 29, 1992 (Box 67)
      - Office of the Vice President for Academic Affairs, (Bob S. Holbrook), 1992 (Box 67)
      - Office of the Vice President for Minority Affairs, (Charles D. Moody), 1992 (Box 67)
      - Office of the Vice President for Research, (William C. Kelly), 1992 (Box 67)
      - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs and University Senate, 1992 (Box 67)
  - Annual Files, 1993
    - Administration
      - Correspondence
        - Cornell, Dick, (Interim Chair), 1993 (Box 67)
        - General
          - A-D, 1993 (Box 67)
          - E-K, 1993 (Box 67)
          - L-Q, 1993 (Box 67)
          - R-Z, 1993 (Box 67)
        - Foreign, 1993 (Box 67)
      - Development Office (Box 68)
        - General, 1993 (Box 68)
        - Public Health Alumni Society, 1993 (Box 68)
      - Events
        - Minority Public Health Conference, 1993 (Box 68)
        - Community-Based Public Health Consortium, 1993 (Box 68)
      - General, 1993 (Box 68)
      - Global Change, 1993 (Box 68)
      - Memos to Dept. Chairmen, 1993 (Box 68)
      - Memos to Faculty, 1993 (Box 68)
      - New Faculty Appointments, 1993 (Box 95)
      - Office for the Study of Aging (OSA), 1993 (Box 68)
      - Salary Appeals, 1993 (Box 95)
      - Secretary of Faculty, 1993 (Box 68)
      - Students, 1993 (Box 95)
        [SR RESTRICTED until July 1 2078 ]
    - Committees
      - Advisory Committee on Academic Rank, 1993; 4 folders (Box 95)
      - Executive Committee
        - General, 1993 (Box 68)
        - Minutes, 1993 (Box 68)
      - Faculty Meetings, 1993 (Box 68)
      - General, 1993 (Box 68)
      - Review Letters, 1993 (Box 68)
    - Departments
      - Biostatistics
        - General, 1993 (Box 68)
        - Cornell, Dick, 1993 (Box 68)
        - Little, Roderick, 1993 (Box 68)
      - Community Health Programs
        - General, 1993 (Box 68)
        - Burt, Brian, 1993 (Box 68)
      - Environmental and Industrial Health
        - General, 1993 (Box 68)
        - Mancy, Hosney, 1993 (Box 68)
      - Epidemiology
        - General, 1993 (Box 68)
        - Maassab, John, 1993 (Box 68)
      - Health Behavior and Health Education
        - General, 1993 (Box 68)
        - Clark, Noreen, 1993 (Box 68)
      - Health Services Management and Policy
        - General, 1993 (Box 68)
        - Wheeler, John, 1993 (Box 68)
      - Population Planning and International Health
        - General, 1993 (Box 68)
        - Monto, Robert, 1993 (Box 68)
        - Takeshita, Yuzuru, 1993 (Box 68)
      - Public Health Policy and Administration
        - General, 1993 (Box 68)
        - Warner, Ken, 1993 (Box 68)
    - University
      - General, 1993
        - Other Schools and Colleges, 1993 (Box 68)
      - Medical School, 1993 (Box 68)
      - Office of the President, (James J. Duderstadt)
        - General, 1993 (Box 68)
        - Academic Affairs, 1993 (Box 68)
      - Office of the Provost, (Gilbert R. Whitaker), 1993 (Box 68)
      - Office of the Vice President for Academic Affairs, (Bob S. Holbrook), 1993 (Box 68)
      - Office of the Vice President for Research, (Homer A. Neal), 1993 (Box 68)
      - Regents, 1993 (Box 68)
- Dean Noreeen M. Clark, 1994-2004
  - Annual Files, 1994
    - Administration
      - Community-Based Public Health, 1994 (Box 68)
      - Community and Government Relations, 1994 (Box 68)
      - Correspondence (Box 69)
        - American Public Health Association, 1994 (Box 69)
        - General
          - A-D, 1994 (Box 69)
          - E-K, 1994 (Box 69)
          - L-Q, 1994 (Box 69)
          - R-Z, 1994 (Box 69)
        - Foreign, 1994 (Box 69)
      - Development Office, 1994
        - General, 1994 (Box 69)
        - Public Health Alumni Society, 1994 (Box 69)
      - Distributed Computing Network, 1994 (Box 69)
      - Events
        - Carol Bellamy Lecture, October 12, 1994 (Box 69)
        - SPH Convocation, 1994 (Box 69)
        - Visit of Brazilian Faculty, 1994 (Box 69)
      - General, 1994 (Box 69)
      - Memos to Dept. Chairmen
        - General, 1994 (Box 69)
        - Dept. Chairs Meeting, 1994 (Box 69)
      - Memos to Faculty Members, 1994 (Box 69)
      - Office for the Study of Aging (OSA), 1994 (Box 69)
      - Secretary of Faculty, 1994 (Box 69)
      - Students, 1994 (Box 95)
        [SR RESTRICTED until July 1 2079 ]
    - Committees
      - Assignments, 1994 (Box 69)
      - Executive Committee
        - General, 1994 (Box 69)
        - Minutes, 1994 (Box 69)
      - Faculty Meetings, 1994 (Box 69)
      - Faculty Review Letters, 1994 (Box 95)
      - General,1994 (Box 69)
      - SPH Review Committee
        - General, 1994 (Box 69)
        - Material Sent to Board of Governors, 1994 (Box 69)
        - Outside Consultants, 1994 (Box 69)
        - Review Comments, 1994 (Box 69)
    - Departments
      - Biostatistics
        - General, 1994 (Box 69)
        - Little, Roderick, 1994 (Box 69)
      - Community Health Programs
        - General, 1994 (Box 69)
        - Burt, Brian, 1994 (Box 69)
      - Environmental and Industrial Health
        - General, 1994 (Box 69)
        - Mancy, Hosney, 1994 (Box 69)
      - Epidemiology
        - General, 1994 (Box 69)
        - Maassab, John, 1994 (Box 69)
      - Health Behavior and Health Education
        - General, 1994 (Box 70)
        - Clark, Noreen, 1994 (Box 70)
      - Health Services Management and Policy
        - General, 1994 (Box 70)
        - Wheeler, John, 1994 (Box 70)
      - Population Planning and International Health
        - General, 1994 (Box 70)
        - Monto, Robert, 1994 (Box 70)
      - Public Health Policy and Administration
        - General, 1994 (Box 70)
        - Resource for Public Health Policy., 1994 (Box 70)
        - Warner, Ken, 1994 (Box 70)
    - National
      - Washington D.C.
        - Conference on Society, Violence and Health, November 16-17, 1994 (Box 70)
        - Public Health Service, 1994 (Box 70)
    - State
      - Community Health Grand Rapids, Grand Rapids, March 10, 1994 (Box 70)
      - Role of Public Health Care Reform, Lansing, April 11, 1994 (Box 70)
    - University
      - Department of Research Development and Administration, 1994 (Box 70)
      - General, 1994 (Box 70)
      - Medical School, 1994 (Box 70)
      - Office of the Dean of Graduate Studies, (John H. D'Arms), 1994 (Box 70)
      - Office of International Academic Affairs, 1994 (Box 70)
      - Office of the Provost, (Gilbert R. Whitaker), 1994
        - General, 1994 (Box 70)
        - Meeting Concerning Annual Review, July 19, 1994 (Box 70)
      - Office of the Vice President for Academic Affairs, (Bob S. Holbrook), 1994 (Box 70)
      - Office of the Vice President for Development, (Keith E. Molin), 1994 (Box 70)
      - Office of the Vice President for Research, (Homer A. Neal), 1994 (Box 70)
      - Office of the Vice Provost for Academic and Multicultural Affairs, (Lester P. Monts), 1994 (Box 70)
      - Office of the Vice Provost for Health Affairs, (Rhetaugh G. Dumas), 1994 (Box 70)
      - Other Schools and Colleges, 1994 (Box 70)
      - Regents, 1994 (Box 70)
  - Annual Files, 1995
    - Administration
      - Community-Based Public Health, 1995 (Box 70)
      - Correspondence
        - General
          - A-D, 1995 (Box 70)
          - E-K, 1995 (Box 70)
          - L-Q, 1995 (Box 70)
          - R-Z, 1995 (Box 70)
        - Regarding Departmental Reorganization, 1995 (Box 70)
      - Dean's Office
        - Dean Search, 1995 (Box 95)
          [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2025 ]
        - Retreat, 1995 (Box 70)
        - Staff Meetings, 1995 (Box 70)
        - Staff Review and Reorganization, 1995 (Box 95)
      - Development Office
        - General, 1995 (Box 70)
        - Fundraising, 1995 (Box 70)
      - Events
        - Board of Governors Meeting, September 29, 1995 (Box 70)
        - Meeting regarding Community-Based Public Health Annual Meeting, Raleigh, NC June 21-23, 1995 (see 1995 Annual Files, National, Raleigh, NC, for records documenting this meeting directly) (Box 70)
        - Minority Health Conference, March 18, 1995 (Box 70)
        - Visit to UM Flint Campus, December 20, 1995 (Box 70)
      - Faculty
        - Citrin, Toby, 1995 (Box 70)
        - James, Sherman, 1995 (Box 95)
      - General, 1995 (Box 70)
      - Information Technology, 1995 (Box 70)
      - Memos to Department Chairmen, 1995 (Box 70)
      - Memos to Faculty, 1995 (Box 70)
      - Office for the Study of Aging (OSA), 1995 (Box 70)
      - Research Council, 1995 (Box 71)
      - Students, 1995 (Box 95)
        [SR RESTRICTED until July 1 2090 ]
    - Committees
      - Executive Committee, 1995 (Box 71)
      - Faculty Meetings, 1995 (Box 71)
    - Departments
      - Biostatistics
        - General, 1995 (Box 71)
        - Little, Roderick, 1995 (Box 71)
      - Community Health Programs
        - General, 1995 (Box 71)
        - Burt, Brian, 1995 (Box 71)
      - Environmental and Industrial Health
        - General, 1995 (Box 71)
        - Mancy, Hosney, 1995 (Box 71)
        - EIH/HN Reorganization, 1995 (Box 71)
      - Epidemiology
        - General, 1995 (Box 71)
        - Maassab, John, 1995 (Box 71)
        - Epidemiology Reorganization, 1995 (Box 71)
      - Health Behavior and Health Education
        - General, 1995 (Box 71)
        - Clark, Noreen, 1995 (Box 71)
        - HBHE Reorganization, 1995 (Box 71)
      - Health Services Management and Policy
        - General, 1995 (Box 71)
        - Wheeler, John, 1995 (Box 71)
        - HMP Reorganization, 1995 (Box 71)
        - Biennial Institute Meeting, September 28-29, 1995 (Box 71)
      - Population Planning and International Health
        - General, 1995 (Box 71)
        - Monto, Robert, 1995 (Box 71)
      - Public Health Policy and Administration
        - General, 1995 (Box 71)
        - Warner, Ken, 1995 (Box 71)
    - National
      - Raleigh, NC
        - Community-Based Public Health Annual Meeting, Raleigh, NC, June 21-23, 1995 (Box 71)
      - Washington D.C.
        - Public Health Service, 1995 (Box 71)
    - State
      - Michigan Public Health Institute, 1995 (Box 71)
    - University
      - Center for Research on Learning and Teaching (CRLT), 1995 (Box 71)
      - General, 1995 (Box 71)
      - Horace H. Rackham Graduate School
        - General, 1995 (Box 71)
        - Office of the Dean of Graduate Studies, (John H. D'Arms), 1995 (Box 71)
      - Human Resources and Affirmative Action, 1995 (Box 71)
      - Medical School
        - Medical Center Clinical Council, 1995 (Box 71)
        - Medstart Conference, 1995 (Box 71)
      - News Service, 1995 (Box 71)
      - Office of the President (James J. Duderstadt), 1995 (Box 71)
      - Office of the Provost, (J. Bernard Machen), 1995 (Box 71)
      - Office of the Vice President for Academic Affairs, (Bob S. Holbrook), 1995 (Box 71)
      - Office of the Vice Provost for Academic and Multicultural Affairs, (Lester P. Monts), 1995 (Box 71)
      - Office of the Vice Provost for Health Affairs, (Rhetaugh G. Dumas), 1995 (Box 71)
      - Other Schools and Colleges, 1995 (Box 71)
      - Regents, 1995 (Box 71)
  - Annual Files, 1996
    - Administration
      - Academic Services, 1996 (Box 72)
      - Community-Based Public Health, 1996 (Box 72)
      - Correspondence
        - American Public Health Association (APHA), 1996 (Box 72)
        - General
          - A-E, 1996 (Box 72)
          - F-K, 1996 (Box 72)
          - L-Q, 1996 (Box 72)
          - R-Z, 1996 (Box 72)
        - Foreign, 1996 (Box 72)
      - Dean's Office